A Guide to the Robert W. Stewart Papers, 1970s-1990s
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Architectural Drawings
  - Robertson Residence, 2041 W. Grace St. 1979 (Oversize 54)
  - Robins/George Gibson (Oversize 54)
  - Robins Unknown Sketches (Oversize 54)
  - Robins Residence, James River Golf Course 1989 (Oversize 54)
  - Robinson Street, 6 North (Oversize 54)
  - Rollins, Leroy Residence, Caroline County (Oversize 54)
  - Ruffin and Payne Blueprints 4/22/37 (Oversize 54)
  - Ruffin, J.A. Residence, Evelynton (with Lee Plans) (Oversize 54)
  - Sauer, C.F. III Residence, 8903 Tresco Road (Oversize 56)
  - Sauer, C.F. III Residence, Goochland Co. 1979 (Oversize 56)
  - Saunders, David N., 3216 Hawthorne Avenue [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Scale plans for library mantel pediment at unkown site (plans in VMFA tube) (Oversize 56)
  - Schwarzchild, Proposed relocation of Charles Schwarzschild Inc, River Road [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Science Museum of Virginia [drawer 57] 1977 (Oversize 56)
  - Scher, Norman A., Cedaridge Rd (Oversize 56)
  - Seipel Residence, 1513 Palmyra Avenue (Oversize 56)
  - Selby, Talbot R. Residence, Chesterfield Co. (Oversize 56)
  - Shakey's Pizza Parlor, Colorado [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Shapiro Residence at Bascobel Country, Goochland [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Shockoe Center, Virginia-Carolina Chemical Co. [drawer 57] 1975 (Oversize 56)
  - Shockoe Valley Historic District (Oversize 56)
  - Shockoe Valley Map (Oversize 56)
  - Showalter Residence, 206 Canterbury, Rd [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Shroeder, Dr. James R. Dental Offices at 7033 Janke Rd. [drawer 57] 1980 (Oversize 56)
  - Site Map for Channel 23 (Oversize 56)
  - Site Plan for Regency Square Mall (Oversize 56)
  - Sixth and Marshall, 408 N. 6th Street (Oversize 56)
  - Skylark Farm, Sign, [drawer 57] 1984 (Oversize 56)
  - Skylark, Beacon, North Carolina [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sloan, Mrs. Anne B. Site Plans [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sobel Residence, 3507 Brook Rd. [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sorrell Association Restaurant (Oversize 56)
  - 9 South Twelfth Street, 1980 (Oversize 56)
  - Southland Corporation, Office Building, [drawer 57] 1968 (Oversize 56)
  - 615-617 South Sycamore Street, Petersburg, Virginia, New Physicians Offices (Oversize 56)
  - Spivey, Sharon and Joseph, Deltaville (Oversize 56)
  - Spratley, Vernon, 312 Roslyn Rd. (Oversize 56)
  - Stewart, Rovert Thesis Project [drawer 66] (Oversize 56)
  - St. Catherine's School (Oversize 56)
  - St. Paul's Church, Iron Fence Enclosure (Oversize 56)
  - Steele Residence (Oversize 56)
  - Stella and Hugh Miller, 2629 Grace Street (Oversize 56)
  - Stereo Column (Oversize 56)
  - Sterrett, Mr. Conrad K. Residence, Queen Charlotte (Oversize 56)
  - Stewart House Color Negatives (Oversize 56)
  - Stewart, Robert W. Residence (Oversize 56)
  - Stewart, Robert W., Interior + Exterior Photos of House, Richmond (Oversize 56)
  - Stranahan, F.D. Residence, Windsor Farms [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Stratford Hall Reception Center Plans [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Stratford Hall, Replacement door for Coach House [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Stratford Hall Reception Center Plans (Oversize 56)
  - Stratford Hall Reception Center 1971-1972 (Oversize 56)
  - Stratford Hall, Admiral and Mrs. Bass [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Straus, Mr. and Mrs. Charles A., Overlook Rd. [drawer 57] 1953 (Oversize 56)
  - 205 N. Strawberry St. (Oversize 56)
  - Stutts, Richard and Nancy, 1814 Grove Avenue [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Stutts Building, 9 South 12th St. 1987 (Oversize 56)
  - Sussex Square: Washington, Monroe, Tyler Buildings (Oversize 56)
  - Swananoa Basement, Noland and Baskerville (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence at Dancing Point (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence at Dancing Point [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence, Dancing Point Pool Pavilion [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence, Dancing Point [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence, Dancing Point 1971 (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor, E.B. Residence, 6000 St. Andrews Lane (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence, 6000 St. Andrews Lane 1967, 1983 (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor, E.B., 5806 Grove Avenue [drawer 57] 1989 (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Greenhouse [drawer 57] 1979 (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor Residence at Dancing Point (Upright Box) (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor, Garland, 8 Tapoan Rd. (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor, Garland, 8 Tapoan Rd. [drawer 57] (Oversize 56)
  - Sydnor, Garland, Garden House, 8 Tapoan Rd., [drawer 57] 1959, 1973 (Oversize 56)
  - Tashgian, Mr. Dick, 1008 S, Gaskins Rd. 1982 (Oversize 58)
  - Taylor, Mr. and Mrs. Eugene, Hanover Co. 1978 (Oversize 58)
  - Temple Beth-El (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer Lot 23, Lockgreen (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer Project (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer Residence [several sets] (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer Residence [ 7 photographs] (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer, William B. Residence, Lockgreen Circle 1988 (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer, William, 309 Sleepy Hollow Rd. (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer, Charles, Bridgeway Rd. 1953, 1990 (Oversize 58)
  - Thalhimer, Charles, 23 Ampthill Rd. (Oversize 58)
  - Thieberger, Fred, Midway Mills in Nelson Co. 1976 (Oversize 58)
  - The University Arts Center Competition (Oversize 58)
  - The University Arts Center Competition (Oversize 58)
  - Thrift, Dr. and Mrs. George N. 1949 (Oversize 58)
  - Tillman Residence, Carolyn County (Oversize 58)
  - Todd Residence, 6207 (Oversize 58)
  - Todd, Dabney, New Garden Walls for 1825 Park Avenue, n.d. (Oversize 58)
  - Todd Residence, 6207 Three Chopt Road [2 sets] (Oversize 58)
  - Tucker Hospital (Oversize 58)
  - Turner Residence, 1523 West Avenue (Oversize 58)
  - Turner, Charles Residence, 1164 Northampton Rd. [2 sets] (Oversize 58)
  - Turner Residence? (Oversize 58)
  - Turner, Preston, 6426 Roselawn Rd. 1956 (Oversize 58)
  - Unidentified Aerial Photograph (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Church Addition (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Elevation (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Floor Plans [several sets] (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified House Elevation (Monument Avenue?) (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified House, Plans and Elevations 1989 (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified House Plan [several sets] (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified House, Elevations and Plans 1978 (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Ground Plans (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Radio Tower (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Residence (Oversize 59)
  - Unidentified Site Plans (Oversize 59)
  - University Arts Center Competition (Oversize 59)
  - Valentind, Granville G., Jr., 31 Blandwood Rd. 1980 (Oversize 60)
  - Van Sessoms, O., 204 Gunclub Rd. (Oversize 60)
  - V.C.U. Hibbs Building (Oversize 60)
  - V.C.U. Hibbs Site Plan (Oversize 60)
  - V.C.U. Dining Facilities [2 sets] (Oversize 60)
  - Village View Plantation, Emporia, Va [2 sets] (Oversize 60)
  - Village View Restoration (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Meeting Center [2 sets] (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Meeting Center 1981 (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia House 1990 (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts [4 sets] (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Egyptian Gallery (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Proposed North Wing (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Plans (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Planting Plans (Oversize 60)
  - Virginia Science Trailer (Oversize 60)
  - Walt Residence, 113 W. Cary Street 1988 (Oversize 61)
  - Water Tower Shopping Center Route 10 (Oversize 61)
  - West End Elderly Housing Project, 2100 Idlewood Avenue (Oversize 61)
  - West Minister Canterbury, new Tool Shed 1991 (Oversize 61)
  - Wheat Residence, 2 Oak Lane (Oversize 61)
  - Whitschey Residence (Oversize 61)
  - Wick, John Residence (Oversize 61)
  - Wiesnenberg, Mr. and Mrs. Karl Residence, 3310 Kensington Avenue (Oversize 61)
  - Williams, Mr. and Mrs. Otto, 1812 Park Avenue (Oversize 61)
  - Williams, Mrs. Walter D. Residence, 4406 Kensington Avenue (Oversize 61)
  - Williams, Thomas E., 5914 Grove Avenue (Oversize 61)
  - Williams, Mr. and Mrs. Julien H., 6429 Roselawn Rd. (Oversize 61)
  - Wiltshire, Mr. and Mrs. William 1979 (Oversize 61)
  - Witt Residence, 7603 Cornwall Rd. 1971 (Oversize 61)
  - WPA Drawings of the Hancock-Wirt-Caskie House, 2 N. 5th St. (Oversize 61)
  - Wray, Mr. and Mrs. Michael B., 1530 Park Avenue (Oversize 61)
  - Wrexham Office, Norman and Freed, 1010 N. Thompson St. 1976 (Oversize 61)
  - Wright Townhouse, 1157 Azalea Road (Oversize 61)
  - Wright, John, 205 N. Strawberry Street (Oversize 61)
  - Wright, Mr. and Mrs. Wesley, Jr., 6020 St. Andrew's Lane (Oversize 61)
  - Wright, Mr. and Mrs. Wesley, Jr., 6020 St. Andrews Lane 1989 (Oversize 61)
  - Yoffy Residence, 6313 Ridgeway Rd. (Oversize 62)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (Oversize 62)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (Oversize 62)
  - Zaidan Residence, 4407 Kensington Avenue (Oversize 62)
  - Zaidan Residence, East Hillcrest Avenue (Oversize 62)
  - 1316-1318 East Cary Rd. (Oversize 67)
  - East Williamsburg Rd. (Oversize 67)
  - 1819 Hanover Avenue (Oversize 67)
  - 2503 Kensington Avenue (Oversize 67)
  - 3700 Mechanicsville Turnpike (Oversize 67)
  - 201-203 North Allen Street (Oversize 67)
  - 1008 North Boulevard (Oversize 67)
  - 108 North Morris Street (Oversize 67)
  - 6 North Robinson Street (Oversize 67)
  - 408 North Sixth Street (Oversize 67)
  - 205 North Strawberry Street (Oversize 67)
  - 203 North Vine Steet (Oversize 67)
  - 9 South Twelfth Street (Oversize 67)
  - 907-909 West Grace Street [several sets] (Oversize 67)
  - 1832 West Grace Street (Oversize 67)
  - 1813 West Grace Street (Oversize 67)
  - 2042 West Grace Street (Oversize 67)
  - 2041 West Grace Street (Oversize 67)
  - 406 West Broad Street 1963 (Oversize 67)
  - 406 West Broad Street, Law Offices 1984 (Oversize 67)
  - 2026 West Main Street (Oversize 67)
  - James River Front Drawings (3 drawings), oversize (Box 1)
  - James River Front Drawings and Designs (2 drawings), oversize (Box 2)
  - Bainbridge Public Housing Complex (2 drawings), oversize (Box 3)
  - Sydnor Residence at Dancing Point (3 drawings), oversize (Box 4)
  - Jewish Community Center (1 drawing) (Box 5)
  - Map of Charlottesville, Robins Residence, James River Golf Course 92 drawings) (Box 6)
  - Unidentified Elevation, Richmond Waterfront, State Offices Satellite ( 3 drawings) (Box 7)
  - Meiller Residence, 6632 Belmont, Bruce Smith Numbers (2 drawings) 1968 (Box 8)